Guide to Armstrong College Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00099
Cubberley Education Library
Armstrong College (Berkeley, CA)
[1929]-1972
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00099
41 item(s)
Located in Berkeley, CA. Founded in 1918 by J. Evan Armstrong then teaching in the College of Commerce and the School of Education at UC Berkeley. "In 1921 the curriculum was organized into five 'courses': Stenographic or Civil Service Course; Accounting or Administrative Business Course; Private Secretaries Course; Foreign Trade Course; and a Normal Course in Teacher Training." (1971/72 Bulletin of Armstrong College, p. 18)
California; Business schools
- The Master Builder: Armstrong College of Business Administration, 1930-1938; 5 item(s) Catalogs for 1930/32-1937/38
- Armstrong College: Accounting--The Intelligence Department of Business, 1929-1932; 2 item(s) Pamphlets for 1929 & 1932
- Armstrong College: Foreign Trade--The Frontier of Business, 1929-1932; 2 item(s) Pamphlets for 1929 & 1932
- Armstrong College: The Senior Executive, 1929-1932; 2 item(s) Pamphlets on management training for 1929 & 1932
- Armstrong College: Three Assistants to the Senior Executive--The Executive Secretary, The Private Secretary, The Stenographer, 1930-1932; 2 item(s) Pamphlets for 1930 & 1932
- Armstrong College: The Merchant Prince, 1932; 1 item(s) Pamphlet on training in merchandising.
- Armstrong College: Commercial Teachers College, 1931; 1 item(s) Pamphlet
- Armstrong College of Business Administration Summer Courses, 1932; 1 item(s) List of classes for June 27-Aug. 5, 1932
- Armstrong Junior College (Berkeley, CA), 1932-1938; 4 item(s) Catalogs for 1932/33-1937/38
- Armstrong College, 1947-1972; 18 item(s) Catalogs for 1947-1951, 1953, 1955, 1957-1960, 1961/62-1966/68, 1970/72-1971/72
- Armstrong College Graduate School of Management, 1951-1953; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1951/53
- Armstrong College Graduate School, 1967-1969; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1967/69
- Armstrong College School of Law, 1970-1972; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1970/72